Guide to the Martin Harwit papers, 1957-1987
Harwit, Martin papers, 1957-1987
- Publications
  - 191. Response to Steven Wolfram, Martin Harwit, in Proceedings of a Conference organized at Cornell University, 1987, Ed. Sander Gilman, to be published 1989. (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - 192. A Crisis in the NASA space and Earth sciences programme, NASA Space and Earth Sciences Committee, 1987. (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - 215. Fourier and Hadamard transform spectrometers: a limited comparison. Part 2. Martin Harwit and Ming Hing Tai. Reprinted from Applied Optics, vol. 16, 1977. (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Books: (Box 21)
    - 1. Astrophysical Concepts, Martin Harwit. John Wiley & Sons (1973). (Translated into Chinese in the PRC). CONCEPTS publishers (1982). (Box 21)
    - 2. Hadamard Transform Optics, Martin Harwit and Neil J. A. Sloane, Academic Press (1979). (Box 21)
    - 3. Cosmic Discovery: The Search, Scope and Heritage of Astronomy, Martin Harwit, Basic Books (1981), MIT Press (1984). (Translated into French and published by Masson in France, and into German and published by Pieper Verlag in Germany) (Box 21)
    - 4. Astrophysical Concepts, second edition, Martin Harwit, Springer-Verlag, 1988. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence with US Government, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence Regarding A.D. White Professor at Large, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Bio Sci 673 Human Evolution, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Readex Microprint Publications, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - History and Philosophy of Science and Technology Correspondence, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - History and Philosophy of Science and Technology Correspondence, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Graduate Program, History and Philosophy of Science and Technology, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Program, History and Philosophy of Science, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Program in the History and Philosophy of Science and Technology, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 50)
- IX. Unpublished Research
  - Shadowing, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Cobe Talk, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Flight Plans, Lines, Sources, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Heterogeneous Universe, 1980s (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Talk on Absorption, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Cosmic Asymmetry, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Trigenred Expansion, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Shadowing, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - John R Pierce Correspondence, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Eureca, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Bell's Inequality, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - The Promise of Astrophysical Observations, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Publications list as of 1997, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Surface Tension, No Date (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Galactic Clustering, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Partical Deposition, Model Flow, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Mass Subsidence Report, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Aircraft Collision Avoidance, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Early Condensation, 1980s (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Interstellar Grain Alignment, 1969-70 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - AFCRL Report, 1964-74 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Antipodal Gamma Ray Bursts, 1970s (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Neutrino Telescopes, 1980s (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Colliding Galaxies, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Transverse Velocities, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Extra Galactic Medium, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Gas/dust Heat Exchange, 1970s (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Hinge, 1980s (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - 0 Point Energy, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - NASA Astrophysics MOWG, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - How much can we learn about the universe?, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Wilson Quantity, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Star Formation, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Australia, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Science, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Cornell, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Chem Book, Age 25, No Date (Box 22, Folder 38)
- X. The Course of Science
  - Letter to Lyme Abel, Course Evaluation, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Learning/Artificial Intelligence/Brain Structure, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - August 29, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - September 3, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - September 5, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - September 10, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - September 12, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - September 17, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - September 19, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - September 24, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - September 26, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - October 1, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - October 3, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - October 8, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - October 10, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - October 15, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - October 17, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - October 24, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - October 29, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - October 31, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - November 5, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - November 7, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - November 12, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - November 14, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - November 19, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - November 21, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - November 26, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - December 3, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - December 5, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - The Course of Science, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Course of Science, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Class Notes, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Notes, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Notes, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Astro 215/A+S 200, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Astro 215/A+S 200, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Astro 215/A+S 200, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Astro 215/A+S 200, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Astro 215/A+S 200, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Astro 215/A+S 200, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Information and Knowledge, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Astronomy 215, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Lecture Notes 1, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Lecture Notes 2, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Lecture Notes 3, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Lecture Notes 4, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Lecture Notes 5, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Lecture Notes 6, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Lecture Notes 7, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Lecture Notes 8, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Lecture Notes 9, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Lecture Notes 10, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Lecture Notes 11, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Lecture Notes 13, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Lecture Notes 14, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Lecture Notes 15, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Lecture Notes 16, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Lecture Notes 17, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Lecture Notes 18, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Lecture Notes 19, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Lecture Notes 20, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Lecture Notes 21, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Lecture Notes 22, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Notes, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Lecture Notes 23, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Lecture Notes 24, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 66)